Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Sandstorm Destroys the Inn
Episode 18
Mr. Slowy, what is our mission?
The drones I sent detected
This place also has this energy
Next
You two go to this place to find this energy
and bring it back
Just take the equipment I gave you.
be safe
When can we catch up with Blue Scarf?
No idea.
Blue Scarf is notoriously cautious
She basically has no flaws
But speaking of it
Even if we catch up with her
we’ll still have to find a way to sneak up on her then.
Isn’t your boss very powerful?
Why do we have to sneak attack on her?
Our boss uses miasma
Although the frontal combat capability is not the strongest,
once you fall into his miasma
You will suffer the pain of losing sight
and then slowly collapse
What about Blue Scarf?
Blue Scarf
Because she’s so powerful
Everyone sees her as a thorn in their side
So she has the most water reward.
Able to easily neutralize other people’s attacks
No one can confront her head on
And it is said that she is ruthless
She once could destroy a town by herself
Destroy a town by herself
This is too exaggerated
Her whereabouts are mysterious
Extremely cautious
Only does tasks with the highest bounty
And never fails
You know so much
That’s necessary
In fact, I only recently became Boss’s subordinate.
In order to become Boss’s right-hand man
I work hard every day on learning these things
The one in front
It’s Blue Scarf
It’s really her
Normally at her speed
There’s no way we can catch up
Could it be
It’s because of that little girl
Sister, please drive slower
I’m still so dizzy
Can we take a break?
Got a fever
Is there a place where we can rest?
So boring
Do you have any gossip?
Have you heard?
Cha Erlang and Blue Scarf have a new feud going on.
It seems to be over a young girl with a bounty from Guangzong.
They’re both top-tier fighters.
Who do you think will win?
It’s definitely got to be the formidable Blue Scarf.
I’ll give you one chance to say that again.
Who’s the strongest?
Boss is definitely the strongest.
Because no matter who comes to the inn
They will all be defeated by Boss.
Exactly.
Our boss’s sonic shockwave
knocks anyone unconscious
Be it Blue Scarf or Cha Erlang
none of them make it out alive
Now that’s more like it
Congratulations
you are our
100th customer this month
we have free—
We don’t need water or food
Just one room
Sure. There are plenty of good rooms
This is our invincible sand view room
Spacious and comfortable
We don’t want this
Then this
What about this room?
Don’t want this kind of room
no problem
We have other rooms
We’ll stay in his room
Live in my dormitory?
Guest, you really know how to joke.
How can staff dormitories be as good as guest rooms?
Okay okay okay
I’ve never seen such strange guests as you.
By the way
Do you have ice?
So you want to eat shaved ice
Didn’t you tell me earlier?
I’ll arrange it now
My sound waves are put into every piece of ice
Just eat
and it will knock you out right away
Such a little trick
Applying this will help you.
Mom
where are we
What’s wrong with me
you have a fever
we rest here tonight
Thanks
You’re just valuable
Don’t get me wrong
Now
They must have fallen asleep
We are ready to take action
Is anyone there?
The third performance today
Toss the ball
There are also performances here
It’s him, it’s her
You are the boss here
That’s right
Distinguished guests are dusty
Come and warm up with a cup of hot tea
Except for us today
Are there any other guests here?
Guests’ information
We can’t reveal it casually
Why don’t you have a drink first?
I’m not thirsty
I’ll tell you after you drink it
Can you say it now?
Is this guest tired?
Do you want to stay in our invincible sand view room?
We both know who the other really is,
don’t we?
In that case, I advise you to leave early.
Who is this inn owner?
No idea.
I know.
I believe her combat prowess rivals that of our boss.
According to many,
if you step into her inn,
you’ll wake up in the desert the next day
with absolutely nothing left on you.
You can’t beat me.
Hand over the guests staying here and do it quietly.
What do I get out of handing them over to you?
The benefit is not getting hurt.
This is my turf.
It’s not your place to run wild here.
Then come and try it.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
What to do now
It doesn’t matter
The more chaotic the situation, the easier it is to fish in troubled waters.
What do you mean?
Just let them get into chaos and we’ll take the opportunity to rob people.
I understand
what are you doing
Didn’t you say there was going to be chaos?
Not this kind of chaos
Why don’t we cooperate first?
I tell you frankly
The other side is Blue Scarf and Xiao Mei
How about we team up to defeat Blue Scarf
and split the bounty equally?
It turns out that person is Blue Scarf
No wonder it’s so difficult to deal with
Remember to split the bounty equally
make a deal
The movement just now won’t alarm them, right?
Don’t worry, my soundproofing is very good.
What was the sound just now?
You seem to get a little better
Then prepare
What to prepare
ready to leave at any time
what sound
Too bad
we chase
We also chase
Hurry, we also chase
Wait
What’s wrong
I feel a little strange
Judging from the suspension height of the motorcycle just now,
It’s different from before
If you say so
There were probably not two people on the motorcycle just now.
That Blue Scarf wants to lure us away on her own
No, so cautious she is
Why did she suddenly take the risk and leave Xiao Mei behind?
So
Neither of them left
Where are they?
behind the box
Good eyesight
I won’t aim here next time.
We will definitely rescue Xiao Mei
That depends on whether you have the ability.
So what?
Same equipment as me
Do you even have the ability to copy?
It’s getting more and more interesting
Power is okay
But the heat is still lacking
Here Weslie
This is right
We need to catch her before Cha Erlang finds out he’s been tricked and comes back.
Don’t run
Let go of Xiao Mei
You can’t leave
Well done. You are truly worthy of being my subordinates.
To be continued